That's what we're experiencing now.
This is a shift.
I truly believe that if we continue on this journey and we continue elevating as a group and connecting as a group in a way that we never have before, that we really can change the vibration and that we really can shift the axis of evil.
But it's not going to happen just overnight.
And it's going to happen by literal commitment and diligence to like, I am going to stay in this.
That's why you see so many people who were like, yo, why aren't y'all posting about Palestine?
Why aren't y'all posting about this on your pages?
Why are you letting the fear continue to stop you, et cetera, et cetera?
Because we know, we know what it's going to take is people going outside of their norm.
That's what all of us are being challenged to do.
And so I want to keep social media being a positive tool for doing that.
Because up until this point, I really was like, I guess this is just for OnlyFans and that one chick on TikTok who makes a lot of money by saying, I see, I see, click, click.
Oh, and tutorials.